Optimizing according to a specific metric is called model tuning,
根据特定指标优化模型称为模型优化
and SageMaker provides a number of ways to automatically tune a Linear Learner.
SageMaker 提供了自动优化 LinearLearner 的各种方式
In this example, I'm considering a scenario in which a bank has asked me to build
在此示例中 假设银行要求我
a model that detects cases of fraud with an accuracy of about 85 percent.
构建一个检测欺诈性交易的模型 并且准确率约为 85%
In this case, I want to build a model that has
我希望模型的真正例尽量高
as many true positives and as few false negatives as possible.
并且尽量减少假负例
This corresponds to a model with high recall,
这种模型的召回率很高
which is the number of true positives over
召回率等于真正例的数量
the number of true positives plus false negatives.
除以真正例加上假负例的数量
So it's going to be highest when the number of false negatives is zero.
当假负例的数量为零时 召回率最高
To aim for a specific metric,
为了优化特定的指标
Linear Learner offers the hyperparameter,
LinearLearner 提供了超参数
binary_classifier_model_selection_criteria,
binary_classifier_model_selection_criteria
which is the model evaluation criteria for the training dataset.
它表示训练数据集的模型评估标准
If I look at the details of the parameter here,
看看该参数的详细信息
I can see that by default this is set to accuracy,
默认情况下 它设为准确率
but I want to change this to be recall.
但是我想改成召回率
A reference to this parameter is in Linear Learners documentation.
打开 LinearLearner 参考文档
If I scroll down, I can see binary_classifier_model_selection_criteria,
向下滚动 可以看到binary_classifier_model_selection_criteria
and I have to select a string, accuracy,
我需要选择一个字符串 accuracy
f1, f_beta, or a number of these other targets.
f1 f_beta 或多个其他目标
In this case, I know I want to set a target value for recall,
我需要为召回率设置目标值
and so I'll set my model_selection_criteria to precision_at_target_recall,
所以将 model_selection_criteria 设为precision_at_target_recall
and I'll also set a value for my target_recall.
并且为 target_recall 设定一个值
So here, I've created my model as usual,
在这里正常创建模型
passing in a role,
传入角色
some details about the train_instance,
设定训练实例
and output_path and my sagemaker_session.
输出路径以及 sagemaker 会话
I've also set the model_selection_criteria to precision_at_target_recall,
我还将 model_selection_criteria 设为precision_at_target_recall
and I've set my target_recall to a value of 0.9.
并将 target_recall 的值设为 0.9
In this case, I'm assuming that the performance on the training set
我假设训练集的性能
will be within about five percent of the performance on a test set.
与测试集的性能相差在约 5% 之内
So for recall of about 85 percent,
所以召回率为 85% 的话
I'll aim for a bit higher, 90 percent.
我将设置更高的目标 即 90%
Next, I've done the same steps as before,
接下来的步骤与之前的一样
training our recall model on our formatted_train_data and deploying the model.
使用特殊格式的训练数据训练召回率模型并部署模型
Then, I'm evaluating my deployed prediction endpoint,
然后评估部署的预测端点“recall_predictor”
recall_predictor and printing out the metrics.
并输出指标
I can see in this case that I have a much higher recall and a much lower precision.
可以看出 现在的召回率高多了 并且精确率低多了
Specifically, I can see that I'm only misclassifying 10 of our fraudulent cases.
我只将 10 个欺诈性交易分类错了
But I am misclassifying a lot more of our valid cases,
但是将很多有效交易
misclassifying them as fraudulent.
错误地分类成欺诈性交易
So now, I'm done evaluating this endpoint and I'm going to delete my recall_predictor.
我已经评估了此端点 下面删除 recall_predictor
So we have a model that's tuned to get
我们的模型经过优化后召回率更高
a higher recall which aims to reduce the number of false negatives.
目标是降低假负例的数量
But earlier, we also discussed how class imbalance may actually
但之前我们讨论了类别不平衡性
bias our model towards predicting that all transactions are valid,
可能会导致模型倾向于将所有交易预测为有效交易
resulting in a higher number of false negatives.
导致假负例的数量更高
It stands to reason that this model can be
所以这个模型可以进一步优化
further improved if we account for this imbalance.
并考虑这种类别不平衡性
So next, we'll discuss one more way you might improve this model,
接下来我们将讨论改进此模型的一种方式
and your task will be to train and deploy a model that's
你的任务是训练并部署一个模型
both tuned and accounts for class imbalance.
该模型既经过优化 又考虑了类别不平衡性